All right, polyamory is, you know, having multiple partners and it's something that's
being talked about more and more just without shade being attached to it. Our caller who just
called in basically said that polyamory is the way to go because monogamy is not only weird,
but it's outdated and boring. But she also said something else. She said that it requires
more work than a lot of people are willing to put in. And I would have thought the opposite.
I would have thought that it was more difficult to be monogamous than to be poly because you have
options. If you're just me and you, you and me, then to me, it takes a lot more work.
I think what she was talking about is not necessarily that you need to be vulnerable
in terms of talking about like all these like deep things about your life, but there needs to be an
openness and vulnerability in being able to share honestly about what is going on between you.
And the more I think about it, say for instance, if you're with someone that's emotional,
then you have to deal with all that emotion. If you have more than one person, I got to deal with
your emotion and then I got to deal with your insecurity. So I get, or whatever it would be
that I could see being a lot of work.
Well, here's the thing though. I don't think in a polyamorous relationship, you're dealing with
every relationship at the same level, right? Like my friend with benefits was not getting my emotional
like stuff that I was dealing with. Cause that wasn't like a part of our agreement. Whereas like my homeboy,
who I'm not smashing was getting that because like, as friends, that was our understanding
that we share.